<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BusTrack</string>

    <string name="title_menu_github">View on GitHub</string>

    <string name="fiveb">Login for 5B \n Username : bustrack5b@gmail.com \n Password : bustrack123"</string>
    <string name="tseventy">Login for T70 \n Username : bustrackt70b@gmail.com \n Password : bustrack123"</string>

    <string name="label_options">Options:</string>
    <string name="label_option_fullscreen">Enable fullscreen</string>
    <string name="label_option_custom_fragments">Enable custom fragments</string>
    <string name="label_option_skip_enabled">Enable skip button</string>
    <string name="label_option_finish_enabled">Enable finish button</string>
    <string name="label_start_intro">Start intro</string>

    <string name="title_material_metaphor">Material is the metaphor</string>
    <string name="title_material_bold">Bold, graphic, intentional</string>
    <string name="title_material_motion">Motion provides meaning</string>
    <string name="title_material_shadow">Light and shadow</string>

    <string name="description_material_metaphor">A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion. The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.</string>
    <string name="description_material_bold">The foundational elements of print-based design – typography, grids, space, scale, color, and use of imagery – guide visual treatments.</string>
    <string name="description_material_motion">Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.</string>
    <string name="description_material_shadow">Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.</string>

    <string name="title_fragment_login">This is a custom fragment.</string>
    <string name="hint_fake_username">Fake username</string>
    <string name="hint_fake_password">Fake password</string>
    <string name="label_fake_login">Fake login</string>
    <string name="label_fake_login_loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="label_fake_login_success">Successfully faked login.</string>

    <string name="title_fragment_custom">Take off!</string>

    <string name="oneTitle">Welcome to BusTrack!</string>
    <string name="onedes">Our android app offers live tracking of bus and estimated time of arrival of bus at a particular bus stop.</string>

    <string name="twoTitle">Unified app for both tracking and as a GPS receiver</string>
    <string name="twodes">In driver mode, We use the app for collecting the co-ordinates of moving bus and store it in the azure storage in a table and retrive those in the passenger mode and analyse it!</string>

    <string name="threeTitle">As of now track two buses in driver mode!</string>
    <string name="threedes">There are two buses that can be tracked, 5B and T70, a testing point has been added in 5B route.In driver mode one should login to the respective bus email ID and password, after that the received GPS data is updated in the azure table every 10seconds.</string>

    <string name="fourTitle">Passenger mode is for the end user.</string>
    <string name="fourdes">In passenger mode, one needs to choose the desired bus and bus stop and also the refresh rate as every time the location of bus is updated a JSON file from google directions api will be downloaded, on pressing check the bus position is received from the azure table and bus stop positions are hard coded, google maps api is used to plot in the map and google directions api fetched the estimated time.</string>

</resources>
